SINDHU PURNOMO AJI

sindhupurnomoaji@gmail.com | +6285726611097 Sragen, January 01, 2002 Karangtengah RT.41, RW.16 Masaran, Masaran, Sragen, Central Java



SUMMARY

A fresh graduate in Computer Science with in-depth knowledge in web development and IoT technology. Possesses strong analytical skills in designing solutions and implementing changes. Experienced in working in teams, collaborating effectively to achieve project goals and enhance user interaction. Interested in graphic design, which supports the ability to create attractive and functional interfaces. Committed to continuous learning and growth in the information technology industry.

EXPERIENCE

Member of KPPS for the Regional Election | 2024

NOV 2024 - DEC 2024

- Served as Sirekap to collect and recap the voting results.
- suring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.
- Ensuring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.
- Completed administrative tasks and reported the results of the recapitulation to higher authorities as required.

Member of KPPS for the Presidential and Vice Presidential Election | 2024

JAN 2024 - FEB 2024

- Served as Sirekap to collect and recap the voting results.
- suring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.
- Ensuring the accuracy and consistency of the entered data.

PT Sapta Cakra Manunggal Yogyakarta (Internship) | 2023

AUG 2023 - JAN 2024

- Developed a website integrated with Internet of Things (IoT) technology.
- Designed a mobile application to enhance user interaction and accessibility.
- Collaborated with the team to ensure effective project execution and integration of features.

Anugerah Jaya Printing (Internship) | 2018

JUL 2018 - NOV 2018

- Edited graphic designs using CorelDRAW for various printing projects.
- Executed finishing processes on MMT products, including cutting and final touches.
- Collaborated with the team to ensure quality and timely completion of projects.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Computer Scince with Honours 2024

SEP 2020 - SEP 2024

Duta Bangsa University of Surakarta

- · Major in Informatics Engineering
- Thesis on "Development of Charity Box Security System in Mosque Raya Assalam Masaran Based on IoT (Internet of Things)"

Vocational High School in Software Development

SEP 2017 - SEP 2020

State Vocational High School 1 Plupuh

• Relevant coursework in Software Development

SCIENTIFIC PUBLICATION

 Development of Charity Box Security System in Mosque Raya Assalam Masaran Based on IoT (Internet of Things) 2024

Infotech: Journal of Technology Information, 10(1), 113-120

Design of Mobile-Based Grocery E-Commerce Application 2022

Proceedings of the National Seminar on Information Technology and Business, 452-454

CERTIFICATION & ADDITIONAL SKILLS

• Certificate of Competence in Junior Web Programming 2024

National Professional Certification Board (BNSP)

• Certificate of Competence in English Proficiency Test 2024 (TOEIC Score : 510)

Language Training Center Duta Bangsa University

TECHNICAL SKILLS

• Web Technologies : HTML, CSS, Laravel, Bootstrap.

• Database: MySQL.

• Tools: Visual Studio Code, Microsoft Office, Canva, Coreldraw.

• Languages : English and Bahasa Indonesia.

SOFT SKILLS

- Dicipline
- Teamwork
- Time Management
- Problem Solving
- Creativity
- Adaptability